dotsub.com 2018-06-30

# Dotsub Privacy Policy | Dotsub

We respect the privacy of our users, content contributors, and translators and want to make clear to everyone how we use personal information that the Dotsub website and service acquires during the course of its operations. We will never sell or rent your personal information to any third party.

#### Information We Collect

We may collect sensitive information about you. "Sensitive information" consists of your full name, date of birth, e-mail address, physical address, phone number, and bank account or credit card information.

We may collect other limited information about you. This may include information about the type of browser you are using, the Internet Protocol address of your originating Internet Service Provider, and your viewing history. We do not connect this limited information about you with any sensitive information about you that we may have.

#### Tools We Use

"Cookies" are small data files stored on your hard drive that assign a unique identifier to your computer so that Dotsub can "recognize" your computer each time you use it to return to the Dotsub website. These cookies help us gather non-sensitive information about your use of the Dotsub website that we aggregate with other information to learn more about how our users interact with the Dotsub website. They do not, standing alone, identify you as an individual by name or Dotsub account number. While you can set your browser to refuse to accept cookies, you should understand that some of the Dotsub services may not function properly if your browser refuses to accept cookies.

#### Other Websites

The Dotsub website may contain links to other websites not controlled by Dotsub. Please be aware that Dotsub is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave the Dotsub website and to read the privacy policies of other websites you visit.

#### How We Use Your Information

We use your information to provide the services offered by the Dotsub website and service; to respond to and process your requests for services and information; to notify you of updated or changed information, website features, promotional opportunities, or services that we offer. We will not send you notices, updates, newsletters, or advertising unless you have explicitly agreed (by "opting-in") to accept such communications. We reserve the right to send you notices necessary for your account with Dotsub to be maintained.

We will never rent or sell your sensitive personal information to any third party. We treat your sensitive personal information as confidential, and have systems, procedures, and policies in place so that our employees also understand the confidential nature of your sensitive personal information. We will only disclose your sensitive personal information to a third party if compelled to do so by law. Unless the law prohibits us from doing so, we will make a good-faith effort to notify you in advance of any such disclosure.

We may allow our advertisers to deliver targeted alerts, advertisements, or messages to the Dotsub website as you are using it. We may provide our advertisers with limited information (non-sensitive information) about your use of the site to facilitate this service.

#### Your Dotsub Password

Your Dotsub password is unique to your Dotsub account and is designed to protect your account from unauthorized access and use. Dotsub will not be responsible for any lost, stolen, or otherwise disclosed passwords. Your password should be protected and should not be disclosed to anyone.

#### Changes to Policy

Dotsub reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at anytime. In the event that we make a material change to our policy we will post a notice of the change on this page, and will notify you of the change when you log in to your Dotsub account.

#### Contact Us

If you have questions about the Dotsub privacy policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#addddfc4dbccced4ede9c2d9ded8cf83cec2c0).
